I eat an entire pint of ice cream every
single day and still maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are some of the recipes I
made this week to stay fit and hit my
protein goal. Started it off by
recreating Ben & Jerry's strawberry
cheesecake ice cream. This one took a
lot of iteration and I finally perfected
it. It is insanely good. Then I had to
do another Ben & Jerry's flavor. Mint
chocolate cookie. Basically just mint
Oreo. Of course it's fire. I mean
anything with Oreos is going to be
great. Then I did chunky monkey, which
is actually another Ben & Jerry's
flavor. If you've never had this one
before, it's banana ice cream with fudge
chunks and walnuts. So I actually did a
chocolate shell to imitate those fudge
chunks. And then of course added some
walnuts. Then to celebrate Thanksgiving
coming up, I did a pumpkin pie blizzard.
This was pumpkin spice flavored ice
cream with the pumpkin Jojo's from
Trader Joe's. Then I did one more Ben &
Jerry's recreation. This is chocolatey
love affair which is a chocolate base
with salted fudge chunks and
chocolatecovered caramels mixed in and
then topped with some salted caramel
syrup. Wait, I lied. There is one more
Ben & Jerry's recreation. This is
chocolatecovered strawberry strawberry
base with fudge flakes and strawberry
jam mixed in. And then I ended off the
week by taking all my leftover Halloween
candy and turning it into protein candy
bar ice cream.